<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<eml:eml xmlns:eml="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:schemaLocation="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.1 http://rs.gbif.org/schema/eml-gbif-profile/1.1/eml.xsd"
        packageId="10.15468/dl.4zkqkp"  system="http://gbif.org" scope="system"
  xml:lang="en">

<dataset>
        <alternateIdentifier>0000607-200127171203522</alternateIdentifier>
    <title>GBIF Occurrence Download 10.15468/dl.4zkqkp</title>
    <creator>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>    </creator>
    <metadataProvider>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>    </metadataProvider>
      <pubDate>
      2020-01-28
      </pubDate>
    <language>ENGLISH</language>
    <abstract>
        <para>A dataset containing all occurrences available in GBIF matching the query:
{
  &quot;TaxonKey&quot; : [ &quot;is Convolvulus lanuginosus Desr.&quot; ]
}
The dataset includes records from the following constituent datasets. The full metadata for each constituent is also included in this archive:
1 records from Base de datos de plantas vasculares del País Vasco: ARAN-EH
1 records from Herbarium specimens of the Muséum d&apos;Histoire Naturelle of Aix-en-Provence (AIX)
1 records from Herbarium specimens, Harmas J.H. Fabre (FABR - Sérignan-du-Comtat) of the Muséum national d&apos;Histoire naturelle (MNHN - Paris)
1 records from Herbarium specimens of Institut Scientifique Mohamed V university (RAB)
1 records from Lund Botanical Museum (LD)
1 records from Botany (UPS)
1 records from Banco de Germoplama del Jardín Botánico de Castilla-La Mancha
1 records from Vascular Plant Herbarium, Oslo (O)
1 records from Relevés floristiques du protocole de l&apos;Inventaire National Forestier de l&apos;IGN
1 records from Geneva Herbarium – General Collection (G)
1 records from Herbarium specimens of Limoges university (LIMO)
1 records from Herbarium specimens of the Muséum d&apos;Histoire Naturelle d&apos;Autun (AUT)
1 records from MBM - Herbário do Museu Botânico Municipal
1 records from Données ONF faune-flore-fonge
1 records from Données d&apos;occurrence Espèces issues de la base Natura 2000 : espèces d&apos;intérêt communautaire et autres espèces remarquables renseignées dans les FSD
1 records from Application INPN Espèces: Observations naturalistes, participatives et opportunistes, fondée sur des photographies
1 records from Catálogo Florístico Histórico de Navarra. Gobierno de Navarra
2 records from Universidad de Oviedo. Departamento de Biología de Organismos y Sistemas: FCO
2 records from Universidad de Oviedo. Departamento de Biología de Organismos y Sistemas: FCO-Briof
2 records from Données naturalistes d&apos;Olivier ESCUDER
2 records from Phanerogamic Botanical Collections (S)
2 records from RB - Rio de Janeiro Botanical Garden Herbarium Collection
2 records from Collection botanique Le Grand A. (BOUM)
2 records from Tropicos Specimen Data
2 records from Natural History Museum (London) Collection Specimens
3 records from International Barcode of Life project (iBOL)
3 records from Colección de plantas vasculares del Herbario de la Universidad de Granada.
3 records from Fundación Carl Faust: Herbario del Jardí Botànic Marimurtra: HMIM
4 records from Aranzadi Zientzi Elkartea
4 records from Herbarium of Vascular Plants Collection of the University of Extremadura (Spain)
4 records from Herbario de la Universidad de Sevilla, SEV-Historico
4 records from Herbarium of Namur
4 records from Herbarium Senckenbergianum (FR)
4 records from Herbario del Jardín Botánico-Histórico La Concepción: HBC
4 records from Institut Menorquí d&apos;Estudis. Colección Histórica de Rodríguez Femenías, Herbarium Generale Minoricae: HGM-Femenias
4 records from Universidad de Navarra, Herbarium: PAMP-Vascular Plants
5 records from Phytochorologie des départements français
5 records from Données acquises dans le cadre de l&apos;activité du bureau d&apos;étude BIOTOPE (1994 - 2013)
5 records from Natural History Museum, Vienna - Herbarium W
6 records from NMNH Extant Specimen Records
7 records from Herbario COFC de la Universidad de Córdoba: colección general de plantas vasculares
7 records from VIT Herbarium - Vascular Plants (The Natural History Museum of Alava)
7 records from Meise Botanic Garden Herbarium (BR)
7 records from Colección del Banco de Germoplasma de la Universitat de València
8 records from SANT Herbarium vascular plants collection
8 records from iNaturalist Research-grade Observations
8 records from Colección de plantas vasculares del Herbario &quot;Jaime Andrés Rodríguez&quot;. LEB
9 records from Inventario de Flora y Vegetación del Municipio de Enguídanos (Cuenca), 2010. Asociación de Desarrollo Integral de la Manchuela Conquense (ADIMAN)
10 records from Geneva Herbarium – De Candolle&apos;s Prodromus (G-DC)
11 records from Herbario EMMA. Herbario de la Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingenieros de Montes. UPM
11 records from Données naturalistes de Thomas GAILLARD
12 records from Jardín Botánico de Córdoba: Herbarium COA
13 records from Herbario de la Universidad de Almería
13 records from Herbario de Universidad de Murcia: MUB
17 records from Institut Botanic de Barcelona (IBB-CSIC-ICUB), BC-Plantae
17 records from Données de la base Ecosphère
24 records from Herbario de Plantas Vasculares de la Universidad de Salamanca: SALA
25 records from Carnet en Ligne
27 records from Données d&apos;occurrences Espèces issues de l&apos;inventaire des ZNIEFF
28 records from Royal Botanic Garden Edinburgh Herbarium (E)
42 records from Herbario ABH (Universidad de Alicante)
49 records from Herbarium specimens of Université de Montpellier 2, Institut de Botanique (MPU))
53 records from Naturalis Biodiversity Center (NL) - Botany
57 records from Cartografía de vegetación a escala de detalle 1:10.000 de la masa forestal de Andalucía
60 records from Herbario de la Universidad de Sevilla
68 records from Localización de táxones botánicos de interés para la identificación de hábitats de la REDIAM (Secretaría General de Medio Ambiente, Agua y Cambio Climático)
73 records from MGC Herbarium of University of Malaga (Spain): MGC-Cormof dataset
158 records from Livre rouge de la flore menacée de France (tomes I et II) - (FCBN)
159 records from Colección de plantas vasculares del herbario de la Universitat de València (VAL).
170 records from The vascular plants collection (P) at the Herbarium of the Muséum national d&apos;Histoire Naturelle (MNHN - Paris)
235 records from CSIC-Real Jardín Botánico-Colección de Plantas Vasculares (MA)
399 records from Sistema de Información de la vegetación Ibérica y Macaronésica
464 records from CSIC-Real Jardín Botánico-Anthos. Sistema de Información de las Plantas de España
718 records from FloraCAT: Banco de datos de los cormófitos de Cataluña
741 records from INPN - Données flore des CBN agrégées par la FCBN
2149 records from Banco de Datos de la Biodiversidad de la Comunitat Valenciana
</para>
    </abstract>
      <contact>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>      </contact>

</dataset>

<additionalMetadata>
    <metadata>
      <gbif>
        <dateStamp>2020-01-28T16:40:45Z</dateStamp>
      <citation identifier="10.15468/dl.4zkqkp">GBIF Occurrence Download 10.15468/dl.4zkqkp</citation>
              <physical>
                  <objectName>Darwin Core Archive</objectName>
                  <characterEncoding>UTF-8</characterEncoding>
                  <dataFormat>
                      <externallyDefinedFormat>
                          <formatName>Darwin Core Archive</formatName>
                      </externallyDefinedFormat>
                  </dataFormat>
                  <distribution>
                      <online>
                          <url function="download">http://api.gbif.org/v1/occurrence/download/request/0000607-200127171203522.zip</url>
                      </online>
                  </distribution>
              </physical>
        </gbif>
    </metadata>
</additionalMetadata>

</eml:eml>
